{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Brick \u0026 Stone Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40101/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40101,"taskName":"Brick, Stone or Block Wall - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Brick, Stone or Block Wall","xmTaskDescriptor":"Brick \u0026 Stone Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":260,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Brick concrete build walls walkway","textMessagingName":"Repair Mason Wall","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes glass block walls. Note separate categories for fireplaces, chimneys, landscaping blocks \u0026 concrete.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes buildings, walls, retaining walls, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Brick, Stone or Block Wall.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Brick \u0026 Stone Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Masonry \u0026 Block Wall Repairs","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Brick, Stone or Block Wall Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Brick, Stone or Block Wall - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Brick and Stone Wall Project","urlName":"Brick-Stone-or-Block-Wall-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Brick \u0026 Stone Wall Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Masonry Repair","searchKeywords":"Brick,concrete,build,walls,walkway,walk,steps,sidewalks,patio,masonry,construction,bricks,paver,mason,stones,landscaping,glass,Block,Wall,retaining,flooring,floor,Stone","emcCategoryOid":-12008,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":412,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40101/":{"taskOID":40101,"originalTaskOID":40101,"setID":412,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1037,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Masonry","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of masonry material do you need repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1563,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete blocks (cinder block)","answerDisplayText":"Concrete blocks (cinder block)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1561,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete block with stucco veneer","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block with stucco veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10882,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interlocking concrete blocks","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking concrete blocks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1560,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Concrete block with brick or stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block with brick or stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":881,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description of the kind of repair you need.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6110,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone/Brick  is loose","answerDisplayText":"Stone/Brick  is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6743,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall is leaning","answerDisplayText":"Wall is leaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6741,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wall is cracked","answerDisplayText":"Wall is cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2764,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gate is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Gate is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2922,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","answerDisplayText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1104,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick is crumbling/flaking","answerDisplayText":"Brick is crumbling/flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3950,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Mortar is cracked, crumbling, missing","answerDisplayText":"Mortar is cracked, crumbling, missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6878,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Water leaking through wall","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking through wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1037,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Masonry","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of masonry material do you need repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1563,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete blocks (cinder block)","answerDisplayText":"Concrete blocks (cinder block)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1561,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete block with stucco veneer","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block with stucco veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10882,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interlocking concrete blocks","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking concrete blocks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1560,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Concrete block with brick or stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block with brick or stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1563,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete blocks (cinder block)","answerDisplayText":"Concrete blocks (cinder block)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1561,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete block with stucco veneer","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block with stucco veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10882,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interlocking concrete blocks","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking concrete blocks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1560,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Concrete block with brick or stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block with brick or stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":881,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description of the kind of repair you need.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6110,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone/Brick  is loose","answerDisplayText":"Stone/Brick  is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6743,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall is leaning","answerDisplayText":"Wall is leaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6741,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wall is cracked","answerDisplayText":"Wall is cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2764,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gate is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Gate is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2922,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","answerDisplayText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1104,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick is crumbling/flaking","answerDisplayText":"Brick is crumbling/flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3950,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Mortar is cracked, crumbling, missing","answerDisplayText":"Mortar is cracked, crumbling, missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6878,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Water leaking through wall","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking through wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6110,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone/Brick  is loose","answerDisplayText":"Stone/Brick  is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6743,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall is leaning","answerDisplayText":"Wall is leaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6741,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wall is cracked","answerDisplayText":"Wall is cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2764,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gate is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Gate is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2922,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","answerDisplayText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1104,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick is crumbling/flaking","answerDisplayText":"Brick is crumbling/flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3950,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Mortar is cracked, crumbling, missing","answerDisplayText":"Mortar is cracked, crumbling, missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6878,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Water leaking through wall","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking through wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}